

Full Stack Web Developer

Summary

Performance-driven and motivated Full Stack Developer with +2 years of extensive experience in participating in all aspects of web app development from conceptualization to implementation and deployment. Always welling to learn new technologies and determined to strong attention to detail, welldeveloped time management skills, and ability to complete all projects within schedule and in a timely manner.

Personal information

Address: Al-Khan, Sharjah, UAE. E-mail: amr.gharz@gmail.com Date of Birth 12th Of July 1991 Visa Status: Residence

About me

A problem solver and researcher. That's how my colleagues describe me. an ambitious visionary who works hard to achieve his goals.

I'm an active person who loves

Now I'm ready to take on a new adventure but this time regarding my professional career.

Language

English: Fluent



Work experience

Mar.2019 - Present

Perfection Group Of Companies - Dubai.

Full Stack Web Developer

Managing the group's Online presence, I built the groups websites from scratch and I am still maintaining and improving them. "Perfection group UAE", "Pile stone UAE", "Modern Supplies UAE" "Perfection Metal UAE".

Sept. 2018 - Oct. 2018 Clic Agency - Beirut, Lebanon. Unreal Engine Developer

> Worked on VR Showrooms for a furniture company hand in hand with interior designers, to deliver a full of functionality virtual reality rooms to insure the best experience to the customers, where they were able to interact with the products using the VR headset.

Dec. 2017 - Jun. 2018 Codi Tech - Beirut, Lebanon.

Web Developer

Codi was my first web development experience, I worked with my colleagues on building websites for NGOs, and we developed the website of "Codi Talents".

Also, Developed an E-Commerce website admin dashboard using PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, Jquery, CSS, HTML.

Mar. 2020 - Present

Umzugshelfer löwe - Berlin, Germany.

Freelancer Web Developer, SEO and Marketing.

I am developing and managing the website and the marketing strategy for Umzugshelfer löwe, which is a moving company in Berlin- Germany. I am mainly

focusing on SEO, social media and Google

campaigns.



Education

Dec. 2017 - Jun. 2018

Codi-Full Stack Web Development Program -Certified by Simplon - France

2010 - 2017

Damascus University

Mechanical Design and Production Engineering

+ Skills

Open Source Contrebution

SiaPrime: I have contributed to an open source project called SiaPrime which is a decentralized cloud storage platform powered by block-chain and smart contracts to end the dominance of big corporations on the cloud storage industry.

Interests

Bitcoin, Cryptocurrencies and Blockchain. Economy And Finance.

Social







